https://greendragonsairsports.co.uk/privacy-and-cookies/

Skip to content
Tel: 01883 652 666
Fly@greendragons.co.uk
Open 7 days a week - For shop visits please call to arrange an appointment
fly@greendragons.co.uk
Open 7 days a week - For shop visits please call to arrange an appointment
Privacy and Cookie Policy
At Green Dragons, accessible from www.greendragons.co.uk, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Green Dragons and how we use it. If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact by one of the methods on our contact page.LOG FILESGreen Dragons follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this as a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analysing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.COOKIESLike any other website, Green Dragons uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.The purposes for our use of cookies is outlined here:Analytical PurposesWe use cookies to analyse user activity in order to improve the website and user experience. For example, we can use cookies to look at aggregate patterns like the average number of visitors or the most popular pages. We can use such analysis to gain insights about how to improve the functionality and user experience of the Site.Your Preferences & User ExperienceWe use cookies to gather certain information about users, such as browser type, server, language preference, and country setting, in order to store user preferences on our Site to make your user experience more consistent and convenient. For example, we may store the recent information you have filled out in a cookie so that we can allow you to easily return to our Site and continue where you left off. In addition, we use cookies to maintain your logged in state when you have an account and visit our Site repeatedly. We may also use your IP address to determine your geographic location at city or postal code level in order to understand our customer reach and market.Measurement Services & MarketingWe use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies from third-party partners such as Google Analytics, Google Firebase, Adobe TypeKit, and PayPal for engagement measuring, marketing insight, payment services and other web services such as data storage and font provisioning. These cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies allow us gather and access information about your behavior and interaction on the site in order to improve our products and services and better understand how you engage with them, as well as to allow some of our vital services to operate, such as taking payments and saving booking information.THIRD PARTY PRIVACY POLICIESGreen Dragon’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of any third-party content providers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.CHILDREN’S INFORMATIONAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.Green Dragons does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.MANAGING COOKIES IN YOUR BROWSERUse the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. You can easily delete and manage any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser by following the instructions provided by your particular browser manufacturer.Google ChromeInternet ExplorerMozilla FirefoxSafari (Desktop)Safari (Mobile)Android BrowserOperaOpera MobileIf your browser is not listed here, consult the documentation that your particular browser manufacturer provides. You may also consult your mobile device documentation for information on how to disable cookies on your mobile device. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this Site. Please note that if you can clear your cookies or cache at any time via your browser and you are responsible for any such actions.ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLYThis Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.CONSENTBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Name
Email
Telephone Number
Message
Please contact me
Green Dragons Airsports
We are one of the original and best airsports training centres in the UK with the most experienced Chief Flying Instructor and a fantastic team of instructors. We offer a comprehensive range of BHPA approved training courses and fun days to the general public. Whether you want to learn how to fly or just want to taste the sensation of flight, we will have the course or activity day to meet your needs. We teach paragliding, hang gliding and paramotoring on our private flying sites. We are the closest school to London, located at Woldingham within the M25 with easy transport links from central London.
What our Clients say
I did the paragliding fun day and had such an excellent time. It's amazing what you can learn in a day! It's pretty tiring so I do recommend you go in good health (although you can rest whenever you feel like it), but it's so much fun. Sid was a brilliant instructor - just the right mixture of pushing everyone forwards while being caring if anyone had any issues. The tuition was spot on and everyone seemed to get a good amount of attention.
I do feel the communications beforehand could have been a bit better (sometimes I had to chase for confirmation emails etc), but I couldn't bring myself to knock a star off for this as the day was so awesome. Highly recommended!
PS For information, Uber will go there from London. Cuts the journey time massively and probably worth it for the morning at least.
Jessica ElkinParagliding Fun Day
"I bought myself and my wife a paragliding fun day with Green Dragons. We had a brilliantly fun day running around a field and had 3 flights by mid afternoon. The instructors were very patient, knowledgeable and we felt safe throughout the experience. With minimal training and no previous experience we were able to fly solo in under a day. You won't regret giving it a go!"
STEVE HARRISParagliding fun day
"I completed my EP and CP course with Green Dragons. Andy is a great instructor focused on teaching you the skills you require whilst keeping you safe. I would highly recommend training with him because he knows his stuff and his flying sites. Their small private sites mean you fly more and learn faster without the need to wait for others to fly first or navigate busy club sites. Thank you so much!"
JEREMY SLADENParagliding EP & CP Course
"I learnt to hang glide with Andy and had a great time. I live in London so originally picked Green Dragons because it was the closest school. looking back now I am glad i choose to train with them because. They use both hill and winch training so i got to fly days when other schools wouldn't have been able to train. Andy is fantastic with a patient but firm approach to training. Thank you!"
silvia snowEP & CP Hang Gliding course
Fantastic day out, had Will as a coach for the day and couldn't have asked for better as really knows his stuff, clear in his coaching style and got me flying in no time. Can't wait to go again.
Chris NormanParagliding Fun Day
I took a paraglider tow conversion course with GD and was very pleased with the experience. As well as being a lot of fun, I was really impressed by the quality of instruction I received. We had a small group (five), but it felt almost like individual tuition because our instructor gave each of us supportive commentary and advice to help us achieve our goals. Good facilities and a great learning environment, backed up by Andy's total commitment, positive attitude, long experience and attention to detail meant that we were all able to get the best out of the time available and maximise our learning. Highly recommended to others!
Richard DTow conversion course
Paragliding in the UK is always less predictable due to the changing British weather, however, once your airborne the frill of free flight is wonderful and worth the wait.
A little patience is required due to the British weather so if your day is cancelled, then a little para-waiting is required and you need to rebook via email. Email is best to contact the club as if it’s flyable then everyone will be out!
This afternoon, I got in five tow flights! This is a risky sport and safety is paramount. The instructors at Green Dragons will ensure you have fun as well as be safe.
Victor MalpeParagliding Fun day
Hi Andy,
Many thanks for a great day yesterday. I had so much fun but I am now feeling the onset of rigormortis – I haven’t felt this stiff since week one at Sandhurst! Please send my thanks to Oleg, he was very patient!
I will no doubt see you all in about 6 years time when my oldest demands I bring him along for a few lessons – he hasn’t stopped sulking that I didn’t bring him!
All the very best to you all and safe flying!
Fond regards,
Claire Masters
Claire MastersMaj C L Masters
Just wanted to thank Andi for a nice and friendly chat and showing me the site and talking through my options to restart flight again.
cannot wait to get back to the sky.
Savalan GHLapsed pilot returning to flying
Best place, best experience and most importantly best coach, Andy Shaw, along with other wonderfully talented professionals in the field with decades of flying time. It is a MUST to go there - truly, you'll love it without question.
Oliver McCourtyHang Glider Fun Day
I bought a tandem paragliding flight as a present for someone and we all had a great time. The Green Dragons team are very friendly and will always seek to get you the best experience, which does involve occasional waiting that can't be helped due to the weather, but is completely worth it in the end. The whole group had a great experience. I was a bystander this time but I think next time I'll be going airborne!
David BrookTandem Flight Booked as a gift
Previous
Next
Contact Us
Warren Barn Farm, Slines Oak Rd, Woldingham, CR3 7HN
01883 652 666
07860 875567
fly@greendragons.co.uk
Privacy Policy
Copyright 2019 All rights reserved. Designed by Green Dragons
Our website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
error: Content is protected !!
